仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
翻译:  冰蓝   洗七里   亲爱的小饭
翻译:  吃货丁小七    猪肉白菜水饺
校对:  借刀杀人赛太公
时间轴:  三水
后期:  瓜瓜    总监： 怀念浓子的瓜瓜
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
摩  登
家  庭
第八季 第二集
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
手机APP搜索
人人影视字幕组
官方APP
更新下载手机搞定
讨论交流登陆升级
到各大市场搜索
"人人影视字幕组"
下载网址：app.zimuzu.tv
早上...好
Oh! Oh. Good morn-ing.
我怎么度过暑假的
How did I spend my summer vacation?
我熬过了跟安迪分手的失恋期
I got over my breakup with Andy.
我在爷爷的乡村俱乐部找了份工作
I got a job at Grandpa's country club.
传染性单核细胞增多症  主要由唾液传染
好发于青少年  具有传染性
-我得了接吻病  -太近了
- I got mono. - Too close!
快戴上你的口罩
Put your mask on!
加州理工从来没有人缺课两周还能跟上进度
No one misses two weeks at Caltech and catches up.
我该怎么办啊
What am I gonna do?
亲爱的  我觉得你要专心想办法
Well, honey, I think you need to focus
变得更坚强一点
on getting a little bit stronger,
更健康一点  然后更远一点
a little bit healthier and just a little farther.
书呆宅女怎么会得这种病啊
How do nerds even get mono?
难道你们是跟同一个枕头练习接吻吗
Did you all practice by kissing the same pillow?
你现在不是应该在工作了吗
Shouldn't you be at work by now?
我被炒了
I got fired.
我打算找到新工作后再告诉我爸妈
My plan was to hide it from my parents until I got a new job,
但是爱耍聪明的艾丽克斯在家
but with smarty-pants Alex home,
我得更小心一点  不然她会发现的
I had to be more careful, or she was going to figure it out.
她病得这么重对我来说简直太不是时候了
Her being super-sick is coming at a really bad time for me.
你昨晚回家很晚哦
You got in late last night, huh?
对啊  昨天是发薪日
Yeah. It was payday,
厨房里一言不合就开始骰子大战
and a game of craps broke out in the kitchen.
看到这块儿表了吗  恩里克的爷爷的
See this watch? Enrique's grandfather's.
你得还回去  还有记住  那份工作
You're giving it back, and remember, the second that job
要是影响了你的成绩  你就得辞职
interferes with your grades, you're done.
你写完历史报告了吗
Did you finish your history report?
边边角角再补充一下
Just got to dot the I's and cross the T's...
然后再补上其他所有字就行啦
and put in all the other letters.
没事的  各位
It's okay, everybody!
我还活着
I'm alive!
开放参观日结束后  我有了段惨痛的经历
I had a traumatic experience after an open house.
祝你们愉快
Have a good one.
糟糕
Oh, no.
周一午餐  周一晚餐
Monday lunch, Monday dinner.
周二早餐  周二午餐
Tuesday breakfast, Tuesday lunch.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
开放参观非常顺利  来了很多感兴趣的买家
Open house went great. Lots of interested buyers.
好玩的事实  在很久很久以前
Fun fact -- Some stranger, probably a long time ago,
有人在你们家墙上写下了遗嘱与遗言
wrote their last will and testament right here on your wall.
放着我来
Trust me on this.
没人发现我消失了18个小时吗
Did nobody notice I was gone for 18 hours?
你们怎么没在制作寻人启事啊
Why aren't you all making posters?
我以为你在办公室呢
I figured you were in your office.
我昨晚很早就睡了
I went to bed really early last night,
我今早起床的时候  以为你去跑步了
and when I woke up this morning, I thought you'd gone for a run.
艾丽克斯呢  难以置信
Alex? I can't believe this!
亲爱的  重要的是你没事
Well, honey, the important thing is that you are okay.
我很抱歉  但是我得去上班了
Now, I'm very sorry, but I've got to get to work.
我们要跟老对手衣柜衣柜衣柜衣柜公司
We are bidding a big job against my old nemesis,
竞标一个大项目
Closets, Closets, Closets, Closets.
这名字让我噩梦重现啊
I'm back in there.
我想住在外面
I want to live outside.
不行  先生  我们不要再争这个事了
No, Senor, we're not having that argument anymore.
毛克利就住在外面
Mowgli lives outside.
毛克利就是他幼儿园里那个
Is Mowgli that dirty kid at his preschool
父母开炸薯条油驱动车的脏小孩吗
whose parents drive the car that runs on French fry oil?
不是  是《丛林奇谭》书里跑来跑去的脏小孩
No. It's that dirty kid that runs around "The Jungle Book."
杰  告诉他不可以住外面
Jay, tell him he can't.
我第一次看《人猿泰山》的时候  也想住外面
First time I saw "Tarzan," I wanted to live outside.
老爸说可以  我就走进森林里  认识了个流浪汉
Dad said fine. I walked in the woods, met a hobo.
他教我用鸟喙开罐头
Taught me how to open a can with a bird's beak.
这故事可没有帮助
That story's not helping!
我非去不可
I'm doing it.
不行  杰
No! Jay!
当然不行
Of course not.
为何要学习自力更生
Why learn self-reliance when the industrial machine
工业机器就仰仗不断的消耗不是吗
depends on constant consumption?
我不吃蛋了  我喝粥
No eggs for me. I'll be having porridge.
你真的还要这么做吗
Are you really still doing this?
这个夏天  我去华雷斯参加婚礼时认识了弗里达
Over the summer, I went to a wedding in Ju·rez and met Frida,
这个超棒的姑娘启发了我
this amazing girl who enlightened me
共产主义会如何消除世界上的不公
to how Communism can rid the world of injustice.
多华丽的婚宴啊
Mm. What a beautiful reception.
可不
Yeah.
对  这不是个好东西
Oh, right. That's a bad thing.
我现在生活很朴素  对我也有好处
I live simply now, and it's good for me.
这可能助我有朝一日亲到她吗  是的
Might it also help my chance of kissing her one day? Yes.
如果这意味着我必须生活在一个
And if that requires living in a world
由政府选择我们所有歌曲的世界  也没关系
where the government chooses all our songs, so be it.
我要端杯咖啡
I'm gonna take a coffee
给装监控摄像头的家伙
to the guy putting up the security cameras.
劳动者需要的不是咖啡  杰  是尊严
It's not coffee the laborers need, Jay. It's dignity.
我要为此抗争
And I'm going to fight for that
直到我擦破手指  压弯脊背
until my fingers are raw and my back is bent.
六个月前  你还因为泡了太多泡泡浴
Six months ago, we took you to the dermatologist
被我们带去看皮肤科医生
for taking too many bubble baths.
给你倒了杯咖啡
Brought you this.
谢谢  快搞定了
Oh, thanks. Almost done here.
慢慢来
Take your time.
重要的是...
Important thing is...
糟糕
Oh, no.
你猜怎么着
Guess what.
我装上监控摄像头的同一天
A black family's moving in right across the street
对面搬来了一家黑人
the same day my security cameras are going up.
这不能赖我啊
Well, what am I supposed to do?
我几周前就预约了
I made the appointment weeks ago
就在这条街上发生了入室盗窃之后
right after the break-in down the street.
但他们会以为我是一看到他们就决定的
But they'll think I made the call the minute I saw them
因为我是个种族歧视的老男人
because I'm a racist old man.
为什么邻居会假设你有种族歧视呢
Why would the neighbors just assume that you're a racist?
歌洛莉亚  歌洛莉亚  歌洛莉亚
Gloria, Gloria, Gloria.
你永远不会理解白人老男人所面临的成见
You'll never understand the stereotypes old white men face.
进了
Goal!
好球  汤姆
Nice shot, Tom.
你想跟我们一起玩吗
Do you want to play with us?
我现在不玩硬汉接触性运动了
You know, I'm off contact sports right now.
因为我玩家庭跑步猜谜时把脚踝扭了
I twisted my ankle playing running charades,
但你俩该准备去上舞蹈课了
but you two should get ready for dance class.
快点去
Okay, go. Go, go, go!
你为什么看起来这么心满意足
Okay, why do you look so satisfied?
是不是刚听到证明
Did you just listen to an NPR story
你某件事说对了的广播报道
that proved you right about something?
不  但你知道汤姆吧
No, no, but you know Tom,
跟莉莉一起玩的朋友
the friend that Lily's playing with?
我听说过  但莉莉还没正式介绍我们认识
Well, I know of him. We haven't formally been introduced.
其实汤姆以前是女孩缇娜呢
Well, it turns out that Tom used to identify as...Tina.
真希望你没有告诉我这事
Oh, I wish you wouldn't have told me.
我本来对自己的性别识别雷达很自豪呢
You know how proud I am of my gender identificadar.
汤姆在学校一直不太顺遂
Well, Tom's been having some problems at school,
但莉莉一直都很尊重他
and -- and Lily has been really respectful of him.
她太贴心了
Oh, she is so sweet.
是的
She really is.
这一切全是她自己的功劳
She gets all the credit on this one.
谁的功劳真的不重要
This so doesn't matter.
是我们教育她要勇于接受新事物
We raised her to have an open mind.
的确  我们也应该被点个赞
Totally. We deserve some kudos here, too.
点的赞够我们每人都有赞了
There's enough kudos for everyone.
"点赞"会是杰出教育奖的绝妙名字啊
You know, a kudo would be an excellent name for a parenting award.
谢谢你  格温妮丝
Oh, thank you, Gwyneth.
莉莉  如果你还在看颁奖转播  快去睡觉
Lily, if you're still watching, go to bed.
滚出去  你个怪胎
Get out of here, you weirdo!
当老板之后就会变成扫兴鬼
Part of being the boss is being a bummer.
一开始心里挺难受  但我逐渐学会了接受
It was hard at first, but I've learned to accept it...
通常都能吧
mostly.
真的很...
It's really been...
玛格丽特  你明知道我就在这里
Margaret, you knew I was in here.
抱歉  我刚收到了一些消息
Sorry. I just had some messages.
卢克的辅导员说
Uh-huh. Luke's guidance counselor --
卢克又在课上睡觉了
Luke fell asleep in class again.
海莉的汽车贷款迟交了
Haley's car payment is late.
还有信用卡公司说
And the credit-card company.
菲尔在一家名为
Phil made a large purchase
应对困难蜡烛网的西藏网站上进行了大采购
on a Tibetan website called CopingCandles.Com.
让创意团队别嬉皮笑脸了
Tell the creative team to get their giggles out.
我十分钟后就能见他们
I'll be ready for them in 10.
但当你上班时一直是扫兴鬼
But when you've been the bummer all day at work,
你就不会想在家也是这个身份
you don't love having to be the bummer at home, too.
亲爱的  你弟弟在吗  我有事骂他几句
Hi, honey. Is your brother around? I need to yell at him.
他当然在
Of course he's around.
他怎么可能会不吵我
Why would he leave me in peace
乖乖在餐桌上写点作业
to do some work at the kitchen table
而不是强行冲进来...
when he could just barge in and --
卢克  关掉游戏
Luke! Game down!
你今年读高三
This is your senior year,
也是你能不当废柴的最后一年了
also known as your last year to not suck.
-亲爱的  -爸爸  你点一下"提交订单"
- Honey. - Dad, you hit "Place order" once,
然后等着确认
and then you wait for the confirmation.
-抱歉  -别抱歉  聪明点
- I'm sorry. - Don't be sorry! Be smart!
那愤怒的怒吼
That angry screeching
是我家新任扫兴鬼传来的天籁之声
was the sweet sound of my new home bummer.
我好累  好痛苦  好烦躁
I'm just so tired and in pain and irritable.
这让我非常生所有人的气
It just makes me so mad at everyone.
抱歉嚷嚷了  妈妈  你为什么打电话来
Sorry for yelling, Mom. Why were you calling again?
我忘记了
I forgot.
去你的  妈妈  下次写下来
Damn it, Mom! Write it down next time!
好了
All right.
我们到了
Here we are.
好  别忘了给放克大师琳达
Okay. Don't forget to give Funkmaster Linda her check
今天课程的支票
for today's class.
-再见  汤姆  -再见  汤姆
- Bye, Tom. - Bye, Tom.
莉莉  你能待一会再下车吗
Hey, Lily. Can you hang back a second?
我不该多待  琳达说迟到的人逊爆了
I shouldn't. Linda says being late is wiggity-wack.
我们只是想知道你在家时为什么
We just want to know why you called Tom a weirdo
叫了汤姆怪胎
back at the house.
我不知道
I don't know.
我们不能取笑跟我们不一样的人  好吗
Okay, well, we don't make fun of people who are different, okay?
-你知道二爸和我有多艰难吗  -是啊
- You know how hard it was for Daddy and me? - Yeah.
我在保守的密苏里州长大  受尽了欺侮
Growing up in Missouri, I was so mistreated
我最好的朋友之一是我在小溪里找到的
that one of my best friends was an old scarecrow
一个老稻草人
I found in the creek.
你的故事要是少说点细节
Some of your stories would be more impactful
会更有震撼力
with fewer details.
好吧  我下次不会了  我可以走了吗
Fine. I won't do it again. Can I go now?
但你明白你做的事为什么错了吗
Okay, but -- but do you understand why what you did is wrong?
明白了
Yes!
心里好膈应啊
Well, this bothers me.
他们本来处得很好  就因为起一点小争执
They're getting along great, and then one little spat,
她下意识就是喷出幼稚无知的话吗
and her instinct is to go all baby bigot on him?
我这话是带着爱说的
Well -- and I say this with love --
但她这整个夏天是和你保守老家的家人
she did just get back from spending a full summer
一起度过的
with your family in Missouri.
所以是要怪我的家人吗
Oh. So we're blaming my family, then?
我只是想说  或许她从那里回来后
I'm -- I'm just saying maybe when she gets back from there,
需要再提醒她我们的价值观
she needs to be reminded of our values.
你懂  反土逼化一下
You know -- un-hick her.
哎妈  土字都上来啦
Oh, the H-bomb!
这大概是针对美国南方人
Possibly the most offensive slur
最具冒犯性的侮辱词了吧
ever thrown around in the South.
是吗  还有...
Well...y--
我喜欢那里的人啊
Look, I-I love those people, too,
但你刚的确也承认了
but you did just admit
他们可能有些守旧
they can be a little close-minded down there.
他们是有点老古板啦
Well, they are a little bit set in their ways.
1980年之前  没胡子的人去竞选市长
It was actually illegal to run for mayor without a mustache
-是违法的  -瞧
- until 1980. - See? It's --
-82年到85年也是这样  -好吧
- And then again from '82 to '85. - Okay.
输入错误
输入
Input.
Input!
请不要再扔遥控器了
Please don't throw the remote again.
我只是在试着找信号
Oh, I was just, like, trying to get signal.
另外几个遥控器坏了又不能赖我
Don't blame me about breaking the other ones.
有一个是意外被踩坏
One got stepped on,
另一个是意外掉进食物打碎机
and the other one fell down the garbage disposal.
这些理由也太假了
You're not even trying.
总之  别再担心你的遥控器了
Anyways, stop worrying about the remote control
担心一下你的狗吧
and worry about your own dog.
她在墙角撒尿
She's peeing in the corner.
说不定你把她留在外面
Maybe if you ever leave her outside,
她就能看家护院  我们也不需要摄像头了
she will guard us, and we wouldn't need cameras.
首先  斯黛拉并不会在墙角撒尿
First of all, Stella's not peeing in the corner,
因为她的如厕习惯是我亲自训练的
because I housebroke her myself.
其次  我的狗永远不需要工作
Second of all, no dog of mine should ever have to work.
他来了  我的老朋友
There he is. There's my old pal.
杰  你最近怎么样
Jay. How you doing, huh?
真高兴你能打给我
I'm so glad you called.
自从跟瑞内塔分手以后我就不怎么见朋友了
I haven't been good about seeing people since Reynetta left.
你听说了吗  她开始跟我弟约会了
Did you hear? She started dating my brother!
今天天气这么好  我们去外面聊吧
Listen, it's such a nice day. Let's go outside.
你家后院环境不是更好吗
Isn't your backyard nicer?
没有啊  只有个泳池和一些椅子
Nah. It's all pool and chairs.
所以你近来如何啊  兄弟
So, how you been, buddy?
我也想跟你说一切都好让你不用担心
I want to tell you everything is okay so you won't worry,
可是情况真的太糟了
but things have been real bad.
你知道有什么能帮助你吗
You know what might help?
把帽子摘了  让你的脸接触阳光
You pop that hat off, you get a little sun on your face.
阳光太刺眼了
Ooh! The sun is rough on my eyes.
我几乎每天都哭
I cry almost every day.
基本上我只有擦枪的时候才会开心一点
Pretty much, the only time I'm happy is when I clean my gun.
生活就是这样  给我一个拥抱吧
Yeah, life, huh? Here, give me a hug.
就是这样
There you go. Oh.
就是这样  杰  你真是个好朋友
There you go. You're a good friend, Jay.
你自己也有很多麻烦  可你还是会帮我
You got your own problems, but you're right there for me.
靠
Damn it!
你为什么需要他们知道你有个黑人朋友
Why do you need them to know you have a black friend?
我装摄像头的那天他们刚好搬进来
I'm putting security cameras in the same day they move in.
这事我很生气  但是被抱抱的感觉挺好
I'm mad about that, but it feels good to be held.
过来
Come here.
记忆重现  恶梦  焦虑
Flashbacks, nightmares, anxiety --
我被锁在壁橱里的经历
My imprisonment in the closet
导致我出现了创伤后应激障碍的所有症状
resulted in all the symptoms of PTSD.
我的保险公司帮我找了一条治疗犬
My insurance company helped me to find a therapy dog
并且同意报销全部费用
and agreed to cover everything,
直到他们发现我不是参军得病
and then they found out I wasn't in the military.
不是吧
Oh, boy.
艾丽克斯  亲爱的你能帮我重启路由器吗
Hey, Alex, honey, could you help me reset the router?!
人家怕怕
Oh! No.
室内开伞要倒霉  要倒霉
Bad luck! Bad luck!!
艾丽克斯的电脑里有她在高中
Alex's laptop had every piece of homework
完成过的所有作业
she ever did in high school.
简直就是传说中的圣杯
It was the Holy Grail...
是这么叫吧
I think.
多亏了艾丽克斯的当年努力
Thanks to Alex's hard work,
我这辈子都不需要学习这词的意思了
I don't know what that is and never will.
不能再来一次了
Not again!
爸  我不知道你在家
Oh, Dad, I didn't know you were home.
海莉  谢天谢地
Haley, thank God.
你能帮我重启路由器吗
Could you reset the router for me?
我也想  可我午饭吃晚了
I would, but I took a late lunch from work,
我得赶紧回去上班了
which I have to get back to work.
-你没事吧  -我没事
- Are you okay? - I'm fine.
我只是紧张导致换气过度了
I think I'm just hyperventilating.
可能过个二十来分钟就好了
Should pass in like 20 minutes or s-so.
好吧  我要回公司了
Okay, well, I'm gonna head back.
我也不能老是迟到
Wouldn't want to be consistently late
结果被炒吧
and get fired, right?
艾丽克斯  亲爱的
Alex, honey.
乖孩子
Good girl.
乖孩子[狗狗]
输入  我知道你能听到我的话
Input! I know you can hear me
因为我看到你闪绿光了
because I can see your green light!
感觉就像在看凶残比特犬跟小鸡
It's like one of those videos where the pit bull
一起游泳的视频一样
swims with the baby chick.
你知道肯定会有坏事发生
You just know something bad's gonna happen.
你的车钥匙呢  我需要从你车借电
Where are your keys? I need the jumper cables.
-发生什么了  -我待了一个小时在车上
- What happened? - I spent the last hour in my car,
开窗听黑人放克乐团的歌  听到车没电
listening to the Commodores with my windows down,
结果我们的邻居都没出来过
and the neighbors didn't even come outside.
肯定是你的黑人好朋友哈林篮球队
That must be your good friends the Harlem Globetrotters.
-你好  -你好
- Hey. - Hey!
歌洛莉亚邀请我们到泳池边
Gloria invited us to sit by the pool
待到莉莉上完嘻哈课程
till we have to pick up Lily at hip-hop.
我的亚洲孙女在学黑人音乐嘻哈吗
My Asian granddaughter takes a hip-hop class?
我们为什么不去前院聊这件事呢
Why are we not talking about this in the front yard?
我们买了纸杯蛋糕  曼尼  吃纸杯蛋糕吗
We brought cupcakes. Manny, cupcake?
我懂了  想拿中产阶级的鸦片堵住我的嘴
Oh, I see. Fill my mouth with bourgie opiates
好让我不能为人民说话吗
so I can't speak for the people?
受不了啊
That was a lot.
他想让一个共产主义接班人的女孩儿亲他
He's trying to get a Communist girl to kiss him.
我们也有关于孩子的烦恼
We have our own kid problems.
今天下午莉莉跟汤姆玩耍期间
I mean, we had an incident this afternoon
发生了一点小摩擦
during Lily's playdate with Tom,
那孩子以前性别认同是"蒂娜"
who used to identify as... Tina.
我不懂你为什么要做这种手势  不过我喜欢
I don't totally get the hand thing, but I like it.
他们吵起来了  莉莉对他说了最不该骂的话
They had a fight, and Lily said the worst possible thing.
那可怜的男孩已经有太多不幸的经历了
I mean, that poor boy's been through enough. Mm.
他父母肯定也经历了很多困难
Oh, I am sure that the parents have gone through a lot, too.
当然  那种事不可能是
Sure. You just don't get comfortable
一下子就能接受的
with something like that overnight.
我问你们一个问题
Let me ask you guys something.
如果某一天  莉莉想当卢[男生名]
If, someday, Lily wanted to be Lou
然后去做了全套"切切拼拼"的手术
and had the whole chop-chop, bing-bang thing,
你们会作何反应
how would you be with that?
-我们爱莉莉  -是卢
- We love Lily. - Lou.
我们爱卢
We love Lou.
-无论她做任何事都不会  -是他
- And there's nothing she could do -- - He.
-他  -无论他做任何事
- He. -There's nothing he could do
都不会改变我们的爱
that would change that.
所以你们不像汤姆爸妈那样需要时间适应
So you wouldn't even need the minute that Tom's parents did?
也不是  也许需要一点时间
Well, no, no. Maybe a minute.
有很多我多年来一直幻想要做的事
I mean, there'd-there'd be a lot of things that I'd be giving up
都不能实现了
that I've always imagined doing,
比如在婚礼上挽着身着婚纱的她走过红毯
like -- like walking her down the aisle in her wedding dress.
-你懂的  -或是低声在他老公耳边说
- You know? - Or whispering in her husband's ear
丫永远别想取代我
that he'll never replace me.
这就有趣了  因为当初
Well, that's interesting, because the minute it took me
我也需要一点时间来接受
to accept the fact that my son
我儿子的生活
was living a different
会和我所预期的不同
kind of life than the one that I anticipated,
米奇尔却说我是个
Mitchell called me an
老顽固直男
old, straight, white bigot.
而如今你们和我如出一辙
And now you're just like me.
我天  米奇尔  难道莉莉是跟我们学的
Oh, my God, Mitchell. Are we where Lily gets it?
难道我们没有自以为的那么开明吗
Are we not as open-minded as we think?
可仗着自己开明对别人说教是咱的招牌啊
But that's our thing -- lording our tolerance over others.
我想这件事证明了
I guess what this proves is,
每个人都或多或少心存偏见
there's a little bit of prejudice in everyone --
无论是你  我
you, me,
还是街对面因为监控摄像头而评判我的邻居
the neighbor across the street judging me for my cameras.
我要去做我早就该做的事
I'm gonna do what I should have done at the beginning --
和他们把话说开
talk to them.
那可不是个好主意
That's not a good idea.
你等着瞧
Watch me!
乔  我不会让你去野外生活的
Joe, you're not going to live outside!
好吧
Fine!
艾丽克斯总是电脑不离身
Alex is never away from her laptop,
所以我每次只能偷一份作业
so I had to steal assignments one at a time.
我并不以偷窃为荣
I'm not proud of stealing,
但我也不是不以我的手法为傲
but I'm not unproud of how I'm stealing.
宝贝  太对不起了
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry,
但既然你醒了
but now that you're awake,
跟我说说家里发生什么事了
what happened in here, huh?
让我告诉你家里发生什么事了
I'll tell you what happened here --
一整天都是这个死样子
the same thing that's been happening all damn day!
我周旋于这些禽兽之间
Me dealing with animals who don't care
他们开着空调还将门窗大敞四开
that we are air-conditioning the outside
坚持要看无趣的家庭主妇互泼红酒
and insist on rotting their brains by watching vapid housewives
来自降智商
spit wine on each other.
而你  连个盘子都懒得用
And you. Can't even be bothered to use a plate!
真是个扫兴鬼  对吧
Oh, she's a bummer, huh?
有什么好笑的吗
Something funny?
没有
No.
你在家做什么
What are you even doing home?
你每周二不是要帮你老板照看猫吗
Don't you cat-sit for your boss on Tuesday nights?
艾丽克斯  也许我带你去散个步或驾车兜风
Alex, maybe you'd feel better if we went for a walk
你会感觉好些  开车带你去遛遛
or a ride in the car, huh? Go for a ride in the car!
这家里让人分心的事太多了
You know what? There are just too many distractions here.
我不在乎我病成啥样了  我得回学校去
I don't care how sick I am. I have to go back to college.
-不行  -不行
- No! - No!
-不行不行  -你当然得回去
- No, no, no, no, no. - Of course you do!
你猜我是不是那种
Was I the kind of person
会强行把病重的妹妹送回学校
who would send her sick sister back to school
只因为不想让她发现我被解雇了的人
just to keep her from figuring out I got fired?
那你猜我在社区大学时
Did I use her laptop
有没有从靠她作业不挂科
to get through community college?
让我送你回去  今天可是周五
Let's get you back there. It's Friday night.
说不定有派对能让你远远听个热闹
Maybe there's a party you can listen to.
-不好意思  无意打扰  -你好
- Excuse me. I don't mean to bug you. - Hello.
你才搬过来  我就住在街对面
You're just moving in. I'm right across the street.
-听我说  -让我猜猜看
- Listen. - Let me stop you.
你早就预约好今天装监控摄像头
You had the cameras scheduled,
担心我看见了会误会
worried about how it would look,
还特意叫你的黑哥们过来
brought your black friend out,
大声放黑人乐队的歌
blasted Commodores.
我也不是第一次搬进白人社区了
It's not my first time moving into a white neighborhood.
-咱之间没误会  -真的吗
- We're good. - Yeah?
该州95%都是白人
我在新罕布什尔州做过实习住院医生呢
I did my residency in New Hampshire.
好  你们有什么需要尽管开口
All right. Listen, you guys need anything, let me know.
没问题  我叫肖恩  顺带一提
You got it. I'm Shawn, by the way.
-杰·普里契特  -杰
- Jay Pritchett. - Jay.
没事的  歌洛莉亚  都处理好了
It's okay, Gloria. All handled.
这是我妻子  歌洛莉亚
This is my wife, Gloria.
这是肖恩  我希望我的发音准确
This is Shawn -- and I want to get this right,
很美的非洲名字  肖恩·舜玳伊缇
beautiful African name -- Shawn M'badawe.
我说的是"顺带一提"
I said, "by the way."
莉莉  我们需要谈谈
Hey, Lily. We need to talk.
其实我刚好有事要出门
I was actually just heading out.
不许逃  请你坐好
No. Sit down, please.
你对汤姆那么刻薄是不对的  知道吗
Look, it was wrong of you to be mean to Tom, okay?
尽管你大爸和我
Even though Daddy and I
偶尔也在本该开明时没有做到
aren't always as open-minded as we should be,
但我们希望你能青出于蓝
we-we want you to be better than us.
好的
O-kay.
不许逃  我们要接受他人真实的一面
No. Listen. We accept people for who they are.
二爸和我会无条件接受真实的你
Daddy and I would accept you no matter what --
无论男女  无论直弯
boy, girl, gay, straight...
不过如果你是女同
though, if you're a lesbian,
可千万得是风趣的那种
please be the fun kind.
我不是因为汤姆过去是缇娜才吼他
I didn't yell at Tom because he used to be Tina.
-什么  -我吼他是因为他嘲笑...
- What? - I yelled at him 'cause he made fun of...
嘲笑什么
Made fun of what?
-这有什么可笑的  -谢天谢地
- What's-What's to make fun of? - Oh, thank God.
他因为这幅画说你们是怪胎
He called you guys weirdos for putting that painting up,
所以我才说他是怪胎
so I called him a weirdo.
宝贝  你怎么不告诉我们
Well, honey, why didn't you tell us?
因为我不想让你们伤心
'Cause I didn't want your feelings to get hurt.
我们怎么会伤心
Get hurt? How?
就因为那个无礼的汤姆不懂艺术吗
Because that rube Tom knows nothing about art?
小卡  她一直在保护我们
Cam, she was protecting us.
但你不必这样做的  宝贝  知道吗
But you don't have to, sweetie, okay?
你不必为了照顾我们的感受
Don't feel like you can't be honest with us
而有所隐瞒
just to protect our feelings.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Really.
你有任何想法都可以告诉我们
Hey, you can tell us anything.
好吧
Okay.
我也讨厌那幅画
I hate the painting, too.
听起来虽然很难受  但本着宽容的精神
It was hard for us to hear, but in the spirit of tolerance,
我们接受一个9岁小孩
we accepted the fact that a 9-year-old
也许不愿意入睡时
might not want to fall asleep
伴着两个半裸的父亲注视的目光这件事
under the watchful eyes of her half-naked fathers.
快通知西斯廷教堂的人  艺术已经过时了
Call the Sistine Chapel. I guess art is out.
你是讨厌壁画  还是单就这...
So, do you hate the whole idea of murals, or just --
快刷
Roll!
绝对很兴奋吧
It's going to be so exciting
要回到到处都是科学东西的地方
to get back to all that science stuff again.
就是烧杯  计算器  激光枪什么的
You know -- beakers, calculators, ray guns.
艾丽克斯  你确定你不想
Alex, are you sure you don't want
在家多休养几天吗
to spend a few more days here to recover?
如果你想的话  你可以睡在我们床尾啊
You can sleep on the end of our bed if you want to.
-对  留下来  艾丽克斯  -睡一觉听起来确实不错
-Yeah, stay, Alex. -Sleeping does sound good.
可不是吗
Doesn't it?
但在那之前  不如先洗一个舒服的热水澡吧
But, first, how about you take a nice, hot shower?
就是希望那一大摞湿毛巾没像今早一样
I just hope that big pile of wet towels isn't on the floor
还在地上
like it was this morning.
你们对我太好了
Aww, you guys are so sweet.
别啊 想想那些科学的东西
No, but what -- what about all the science stuff?
那些好玩的  比如用实验室护目镜头带
All the fun. You know -- snapping each other in the butts
-互相弹对方的屁股  -其实呢
- with your goggle straps. - You know what?
在这里多留上几天
Staying here a few more days
也许有助我快点恢复健康
may help me kick this sickness a little faster.
这就对了嘛  等一下
There you go. Wait a second.
我记得我不是已经把我的电脑打包进去了吗
I thought I already packed my laptop.
为什么它会在走廊的桌子上
Why is it on the hallway table?
时间万物为何会出现在它出现的地方
Uh, why is anything anywhere?
为什么我们的脚不是在胳膊的后面
Why aren't our feet at the end of our arms?
谁打开了我高三写的《愤怒的葡萄》论文
Who opened my 12th-grade "Grapes of Wrath" essay?
天啊  你想要我留在家
Oh, my God. You just want me to stay here
是为了偷我以前的高中作业
so you can steal all of my old homework.
我迫不及待要听你
Wow. I can't wait to hear what you have
对他这次做错事有何看法
to say about this lapse in judgment.
这也比妈妈在做的事情好多了
Hey, it's better than what Mom's doing.
她在利用你来教训我们
She's just using you to yell at us.
我认为这句顶嘴就该扼杀在摇篮里
I would nip that back talk in the bud.
真不敢相信  他说的是真的
I can't believe it. He's right!
亲爱的  你又开始不开心了
Honey, you're getting upset again.
快来  我们去给你拿零食
Come on. Let's go get a treat.
不要那么抚摸我  还有带我散步之类的
Stop with the petting and -- and the walks.
你就是把我当成一条治疗犬
You're using me as a therapy dog.
这完全是无稽之--
That's ridiculi--
我有吗
Am I?
那卢克干的好事怎么说
Well...what about what Luke's doing?
我们已经处理过他的问题了
We just dealt with him.
还有  海莉
And, Haley...
你是这个家里唯一真正关心我的人
you are the only one who really cares about me.
就这么决定了  我要回学校
That's it! I'm going back to school.
我开车送你  宝贝
I will drive you, sweetie.
艾丽克斯  不要  停下  别动
Alex, no. Stop! Stay!
快跟我说  让人类停下来是怎么说来着
How do you ask a human not to go, again?
-艾丽克斯  等等  -对  等等
-Alex, wait! -Right.
我们不是不走  她就是停下来喘口气
We're still leaving. She's just catching her breath.
别这样  我感觉好糟糕  我没意识到自己犯错
Come on. I feel so bad. I had no idea what I was doing.
那我就感觉更糟糕了  我是明知故犯
I feel worse. I really, really knew what I was doing.
我们家又病又可怜的闺女
Our poor sick daughter.
我们应该好好照顾她的
We should be taking care of her.
所以我们是认识到错误就够了
So, is knowing all this enough,
还是需要做点实际的举动呢
or do we have to, like, do something?
我看得都心碎了
Breaks my heart.
我看我得辞掉工作  回来照顾她到康复
I should quit my job and nurse her back to health.
你被辞退了  对吧
You got fired, didn't you?
艾丽克斯不得不休学一学期
Alex had to take the semester off.
我有些失望完全是因为她有些失望
I was disappointed 'cause she was disappointed,
不过我又有点暗爽她能多留在家久一点
but I was also kind of happy to have her home a little longer.
口罩戴上
Aww. Mask!
小卡
Cam?
我就是想告诉她
Oh, I just wanted to tell her how proud I was
我为她今天的表现感到很骄傲
of how she handled herself today,
但她已经睡着了
but she's already asleep. Well,
你可以等她明天醒来再告诉她  好吗
you can tell her in the morning, okay?
对了  我读到一个关于
Oh, by the way, I found an article online
黑山人艺术修复家族的文章...
about a family of Montenegrin art restorers --
算了  宝宝  快走吧  别想它了
Let it go, babe. Come on. Come on.
小卡
Oh, Cam.
看她多有心
Look what she did.
杰  你在干吗  快回房睡觉吧
Jay, what are you doing? Come to bed.
我有这些最先进技术的摄像头
I've got these new state-of-the-art cameras.
我想我可以回顾一下这一整天
I thought I'd review the day,
我们的邻居到底瞪了我们多少次
see how many times our neighbor glared at us.
等等
Wait a second.
那个是曼尼在舔垃圾箱里杯子蛋糕的包装纸吗
Is that Manny licking cupcake wrappers from the trash?
我就知道他会屈服
I knew he'd fold.
这疯狂的舔势  看起来都有点色情了
Ah, the vigor. It's almost pornographic.
这些摄像头到处都有吗
Are these cameras everywhere?
是啊  刚才那个是垃圾箱周围
Yeah. That's the garbage area.
我们还能看到后院  前门
Then we got the backyard, front door.
再就是里面  等等
Go inside. Wait.
原来是乔在角落尿尿  不是斯黛拉
That's Joe peeing in the corner, not Stella.
没事了 他已经住在院子里的
That's it. He lives outside now.
快走吧  我们从摄像头里看着他就行了
Come. We'll watch him from the cameras.
等一下
Hold on.
你这是有病啊
You have a problem.
我要去给你搞那种橡胶遥控器
I'm gonna get you one of those rubber remotes,
就是幼儿园
they put in nursery schools
-还有疯人院用的那种  -谢谢
- and insane asylums. - Thank you.